<resources>
    <string name="app_name">learn</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first">FirstActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="access_token">pk.eyJ1IjoiaW1sbHQiLCJhIjoiY2piNHk5eGdwMDh5ZTM0cndod3plNXhqcyJ9.17UDSHDRaItu3BTJwnpPKA</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">detailActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="lfs">
        "  位于南昌市老城区东南方，南昌火车站西面400米处，建在市区南北主干道八一大道、井冈山大道上，由福山立交与坛子口立交组成。"
        "  是南昌市交通咽喉及枢纽部位，也是连接火车站的主要进出口。\n"
        "  老福山立交桥为环形主体桥，一层通道，设有7个地下口部房，安装了8部自动扶梯，连通福山地下商场；二层为地面，三层环桥分别设有4条单向通道，4条双向通道，与上下层道路相接。"
        "  三层环桥与高桥相接，设有1条双向通道，6条单向通道分别与一、二层路面相接。福山环桥为R60米圆环，桥面净宽15.88米。\n"
        "  坛子口环形桥为R34米的近圆椭圆，桥面净宽为12.88米，高架桥跨福山环桥为R—450米曲线内，桥面宽15.88米。福山-坛子口立交共设15条通道，双向通道分别宽15.88米、19.88米、9.88米，单向通道宽为7.88米。立交桥上部结构为钢筋混凝土连续梁。"
        "  高架桥跨福山环桥段设六跨钢筋混凝土连续梁，长度为204米。其他部分各通道均为18米钢筋混凝土箱梁。\n"
        "  下部结构为单桩支单点支撑。连接处过渡墩及下引线高架桥段设有双柱式多柱。福山圆环内设有街心花园，内有彩色喷泉。高架桥总建筑面积7.6万平方米，中心轴线长6200米，总投资1.3亿元。"
    </string>
    <string name="bygc">
        "  位于江西省南昌市东湖区，为南昌市的心脏地带，江西省最大的城市中心广场，南昌市和江西省政治、经济、文化、休闲、娱乐等活动的重要场所，原名人民广场。\n"
        "  东西宽为280米，南北长为437米，由中心广场、主席台、东西二块游园组成，占地总面积122588平方米。其中广场中心面积为55239平方米，广场主席台14739平方米，广场东游园27742平方米，广场西游园24868平方米。"
        "广场中心的大型音乐彩色喷泉，喷泉直径50米，水容量1945立方米，标志着长治1945年的解放。446盏红、黄、蓝水下泛光灯。1290个喷头再现八路军129师在太行浴血奋战的画面，随着音乐的节拍，每20秒喷出一组花样。池中央的三个主喷头，喷高为36.9米寓意着长治经济腾飞、繁荣昌盛。\n"
        "  八一广场伫立着由叶剑英元帅题写的“八一南昌起义纪念塔”，广场集万宠于一身，文化、商贸、娱乐、休闲、餐饮、服务等在此各展魅力，是通往城市四方的直通大道，是江西省南昌市民活动的中心。"
    </string>
    <string name="sjt">
        "  位于江西省南昌市西湖区绳金塔街东侧，原南昌城进贤门外，始建于唐天祐年间（公元904～907年），相传建塔前异僧惟一掘地得铁函一只，内有金绳四匝，古剑三把（分别刻有“驱风”、“镇火”、“降蛟”字样），还有金瓶一个，盛有舍利子三百粒，绳金塔因此而得名。\n"
        "  绳金塔古朴秀丽，具有中国江南建筑的典型艺术风格，自唐代始建至今，已有1100多年的历史，是历史信息的载体，是古代中国劳动人民智慧的结晶。绳金塔素有“水火既济，坐镇江城”之说，是南昌人的镇城之宝。"
    </string>
    <string name="bydd">

        "  始建于上世纪20年代（民国17年），原名安石路，是在古南昌城墙的地基上修建的一条马路。\n"
        "  1951年，被提出在南昌市城东面城墙废墟上开辟一条81米宽的八一大道，并修建60米宽的井冈山大道继续向南延伸，当时与北京长安街不相上下，甚至比长安街还要宽，曾被称作中国第一宽大道，因为舆论而被迫压缩至61米。\n"
        "  1956年，61米的八一大道完成，成为当时全国仅次于北京长安街的一条大道，当时的省长邵式平很聪明的预留了拓宽空间，在人行道上下足功夫。"
        "这条上世纪50年代扩建的大道，到50多年后依然适用，它为南昌乃至江西的交通和经济发展起着重要作用。"
        "  但遗憾的是，如今的八一大道果然严重超负荷，而上世纪预留的人行道也未使用拓宽。"
        "  该大道如今为南昌市的一条南北主干道，南起老福山，北至青山路口，著名的八一广场恰好座落于八一大道中点。\n"
        "  八一大道的路基民国时期是南昌旧城墙，后拆毁城墙修建了号称南昌的长安街的大道，这是一条宽60米以上的十里长街，沿街两边有不少南昌的著名建筑。"

    </string>
    <string name="byq">

        "  建成于1936年，原名中正桥，系木面桥梁。1949年全国解放后，对大桥进行了改建，并更名为“八一桥”。1997年9月29日，新的南昌八一大桥于正式建成通车。它东起阳明路，跨越赣江，西接庐山南大道，北连昌北开放开发区，接昌九高速公路。是连接湘、鄂、皖及赣北各地的重要通道。\n"
        "  由主桥、引桥、引道三部分组成，全长约6公里，其中主桥1040米、南引桥2017米、北桥1314米。桥面有效宽度26米，双向四车道，设计速度为每小时60公里，是江西省第一座斜拉桥，也是南昌最长的一条斜拉索桥。整座大桥宛如巨龙横卧在赣江之上，成了南昌一道新的风景线。"

    </string>
    <string name="hcz">
        "  中华民国期间为浙赣铁路（始建于清末1899年）南昌支线的一个尽头站，由浙（浙江省）赣（江西省）两省府，铁道部及银行，组织浙赣铁路联合公司，下设浙赣铁路局，继续向西修建形成该时中国最重要的铁路运输线，是该时中国“八纵八横”铁路网的主骨架，老南昌称为南站。\n"
        "  日本侵华时期，日军首要侵占南昌后，首先中断中国的重要铁路运输，断送浙赣线来往车辆途经当时的首都南京及上海、杭州和北上的天津，奉天（沈阳）等线，导致国内出现粮食灾荒等人为灾难现象。\n"
        "  南昌站于位于昌北的牛行车站相对应，南昌火车站当时负责浙赣方向的车，而牛行车站只负责南浔铁路的到发任务，此状一直持续到中华人民共和国的建立，南昌需要另外一座跨江大桥，于是拉通南浔铁路和浙赣铁路的赣江大桥在1963年6月完工，随后南昌火车站成为南浔铁路和浙赣铁路南昌支线的共用车站，牛行车站随即被弃用。\n"
        "  牛浔铁路牛行到南昌水泥厂段成为了废弃的铁路，并且大部分被拆除，现在的红谷滩以及保利高尔夫花园占用了大部分该段铁路的路基。\n"
        "  这种状况一直到了90年代发生改变，随着京九铁路的建设，使得南昌火车站成为了瓶颈，于是在90年代中期老站被拆除，在1996年完工，南昌火车站旧貌变新颜，变成了现在的模样。但车站西广场直到2007年才完成改造，站前亦建造了车站地标世界球。\n"
        "  目前南昌火车站附近的洛阳路下穿隧道工程，将大大改变南昌火车站旁边的交通状况，将于2010年10月1日完工。\n"
        "  南昌站（城站火车站）是中国铁路枢纽最重要车站之一，中国规模最大的人口集散地之一，位于京九铁路正线上【其中南昌-向塘(西)段亦可作为浙赣铁路的支线】，并通过联络线连接了沪昆高速线、昌九城际线、昌福线等线路，是华东地区的重要铁路枢纽站之一。据统计，南昌火车站2004年日均发送旅客达到3万人次，高峰日达到7.46万人次。\n"
        "  南昌站已成为南昌向全国、全世界传递信息的重要窗口；南昌站出发的列车覆盖华南、华中、华东、华北、东北、西北、西南地区的主要城市。\n"
        "  1996年初竣工的南昌站建筑整体结构气势磅礴，包括客运站房、铁路引入线、市政道路及立交桥、地铁、铁路自动化通讯系统以及与其相配套的建筑群如邮政枢纽、公安等工程，建成时以189公尺楼高荣登中国卖场面积最大的车站大楼纪录，是一座融行车指挥、购票、行包托运、客运服务和商业、餐饮、住宿、娱乐等多功能于一体的设施完善的现代化大型新客站。"
    </string>
</resources>
